The Guide to the John Canemaker Animation Collection 1903-2012 (Bulk 1970-2000) MSS 040
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Accretions 2008 - Series VI: Major Projects
  - Subseries B: "The Animated Raggedy Ann & Andy"
    - Canemaker, John: Correspondence: various related to research, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 142)
    - Canemaker, John: Interviews: various related to research, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 143)
    - Canemaker, John: Interviews: various related to research, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 144)
    - Canemaker, John: Notes on studio visits, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 145)
    - Gruelle, Worth, 1976 - 1977 (Box 4, Folder 146)
    - Williams, Dick, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 147)
    - The PEG-BOARD: Vol. 7, Nos. 2, 3, 5, 7 & 8, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 148)
    - Miscellaneous articles, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 149)
  - Subseries C: "Walt Disney's Nine Old Men and the Art of Animation"
    - Book reviews, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 150)
    - Correspondence: various related to book, 2001 - 2004 (Box 4, Folder 151)
    - Publicity: various related to book, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 152)
- Accretions 2008 - Series VII: Objects
  - Disney, Walt: CHICKEN RUN, 2000 (Box 8)
- Accretions 2008 - Oversize - Series I: Documentary Material
  - Subseries A: Subjects
    - WAAW Studio: TEEN BII, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 158)
  - Subseries B: People
    - Disney, Walt: FANTASIA ***see also*** Series I-A, Box 1, Folder 4, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 159)
    - Disney, Walt: Walt Disney Family Museum, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 160)
    - McCay, Winsor: Wonderland and Eden Musee (Box 5, Folder 161)
- Accretions 2012 - Series I: Documentary Material
  - Subseries A: Subjects
    - The 1978 Los Angeles International Film Exposition (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Animation Who and Where - Joe Campana [1 of 4], 2012 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Animation Who and Where - Joe Campana [2 of 4], 2012 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Animation Who and Where - Joe Campana [3 of 4], 2012 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Animation Who and Where - Joe Campana [4 of 4], 2012 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Calendar - Jacob Burns Film Center, January/February 2004 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Celebrating the International Museum of Cartoon Art Collection, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Company - The Original Cast in Concert, April 1993 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Data/Interviews for Article on 2D vs. 3D Animation, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Drawings for Animated Films 1914-1978, c.1 and c.2 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Forbidden Animation, undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Ghetto Film School 2010 & 2011 - John Canemaker Guest Lectures, 2009-2011 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - 2010 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Irish Animation Research & Article by John Canemaker for Print Magazine Oct. 2010, 1989; 2008-2010 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - The John Basmajian Collection of Walt Disney Animation Art - Christie's East, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Kinetica-2: A Centennial Tribute to Oskar Fischinger, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Lincoln Center's Walt Disney - 50th Anniversary Film Retrospective, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Mickey Mouse 1928-1978 The Bowers Museum (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - The Moving Image, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - "My Depression", 2005; 2009 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Nordisk Tidskrift on Animerad Film Story Board, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - NYU Tenure Docket [1 of 5], 1979-1992 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - NYU Tenure Docket [2 of 5], 1979-1992 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - NYU Tenure Docket [3 of 5], 1979-1992 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - NYU Tenure Docket [4 of 5], 1979-1992 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - NYU Tenure Docket [5 of 5], 1979-1992 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - OpenEnded Group, 1998-2009 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - South Beach, FL Festival, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Visionfest 2005 Student Animation Competition (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Walt Disney Family Museum - opened S.F. 10/1/09, 2006-2009 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Subseries B: People
    - Bachert, Hildegard - A Memoir, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Canemaker, John - Article for D23 (Disney Magazine) Spring 2012, 2009-2012 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Canemaker, John - in Rio de Janeiro, Brazil Aug. 28 (Mon.) - Sept. 3 (Sun.) 1995. 7th Banco Nacional Int'l Film Festival (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Canemaker, John - Introduction to 2012 Book of Mary Blair. Artwork for Golden Books., 2011 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Canemaker, John - NYU Distinguished Teaching Award, 2008-2009 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Canemaker, John - Personal Diaries, Notes, Photos [1 of 3], 2006-2012 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Canemaker, John - Personal Diaries, Notes, Photos [2 of 3], 2006-2012 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Canemaker, John - Personal Diaries, Notes, Photos [3 of 3], 2006-2012 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Canemaker, John - Teaching in Ireland Nov. 2009. Correspondence, Programs, Itinerary, Etc. (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Natwick, Grim - The Art of Grim Natwick - Howard Lowery, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Accretions 2012 - Series IV: Periodical Collection
  - 17th World Festival of Animated FIlm - Catalog, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - 17th World Festival of Animated Film - Catalog: Films, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - The 35th Annual Annie Awards, 2008 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Aiga: Journal of Graphic Design vol. 16 no. 1, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Animation Newsletter [Bob Karin] [1 of 3], 1984 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Animation Newsletter [Bob Karin] [2 of 3], 1984 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Animation Newsletter [Bob Karin] [3 of 3], 1984 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Animato! no. 21 (Spring 1991), no. 31 (Winter 1995), 1991; 1995 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Animator - no. 19 (Apr/Jun 1987) (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Cartoonist Profiles - no. 20 (Dec. 1973), no. 23 (Sept. 1974), no. 25 (Mar. 1975), 1973; 1974; 1975 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Cartoonist Profiles - no. 33 (March 1977), no. 34 (June 1977) (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Cartoonist Profiles - no. 35 (Sept. 1977), no. 37 (Mar. 1978), 1977; 1978 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Cartoonist Profiles - no. 39 (Sept. 1978), no. 41 (Mar. 1979), 1978; 1979 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Cartoonist Profiles - no. 42 (June 1979), no. 43 (Sept. 1979) (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Cartoonist Profiles - no. 44 (Dec. 1979), no. 45 (March 1980), 1979; 1980 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Cartoonist Profiles - no. 48 (Dec. 1980), no. 49 (March 1981), 1980; 1981 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Cartoonist Profiles - no. 57 (March 1983), no. 63 (Sept. 1984), 1983; 1984 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Cartoonist Profiles - no. 64 (Dec. 1984), no. 65 (March 1985), 1984; 1985 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Cartoonist Profiles - no. 67 (Sept. 1985), no. 68 (Dec. 1985) (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Cartoonist Profiles - no. 70 (June 1986), no. 74 (June 1987), 1986; 1987 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Cartoonist Profiles - no. 75 (Sept. 1987) (2 copies) (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Christmas of '85 - Alexander Gallery, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Christmas of '86 - Alexander Gallery, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Collectors' Showcase - vol. 18 no. 5 (Sept./Oct. 1998), vol. 20 no. 1 (Jan./Feb. 2000), 1998; 2000 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - The Comic Art Show - Whitney Museum of American Art - Summer 1983 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - The Comics Journal - The Magazine of News and Criticism - no. 120 (March 1988) (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Deep Focus - vol. 2 no. 2 (3 copies), 1989 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Disney Magazine (Fall 2001, Summer 2002), 2001; 2002 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Disney Magazine (Fall 2003) (2 copies) (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Esopus (Fall 2011) (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Fantioche - 1st International Animation Film Festival, Baden/Switzerland (Oct. 1995) (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Fantioche - 2nd International Animation Film Festival, Baden/Switzerland (Sept. 1997) (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Filmmakers Newsletter - vol. 7 no. 3 (Jan. 1974), vol 7 no. 6 (Apr. 1974) (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Filmmakers Newsletter - vol. 7 no. 8 (June 1974), vol. 8 no. 3 (Jan. 1975), 1974; 1975 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Fine Animation Art & Related Items - Howard Lowery (2 copies), 1990 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Graphis 296, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Horizon: The Magazine of the Arts (March 1980) (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Insight (Dec. 1988) (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Jesús Carles Villallonga - Antològica 1945-1976 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Kodak Professional Forum - vol. 6, no. 1 (two copies), 1983 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - L'Officiel - Festival International Du Film D'Animation, 2008 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Memories - The Magazine of Then and Now (Feb./March 1990) (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - The Movie - The Illustrated History of the Cinema - Chapter 33, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - New York University Magazine (Fall 1989) (two copies) (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Platform International Animation Festival, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Print - America's Graphic Design Magazine (March/Apr. 1983) (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Print - America's Graphic Design Magazine (Jan./Feb. 1988) (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Print - America's Graphic Design Magazine (May/June 1989) (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Print - America's Graphic Design Magazine (Sept./Oct. 1990) (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Print - America's Graphic Design Magazine (March/Apr. 1993) (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Print - America's Graphic Design Magazine (Sept./Oct. 1994) (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Print - America's Graphic Design Magazine (Jan./Feb. 1995) (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Print - America's Graphic Design Magazine (March/Apr. 1996) (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Print - America's Graphic Design Magazine (May/June 1998) (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Print - America's Graphic Design Magazine (May/June 2000) (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Print - America's Graphic Design Magazine (July/Aug. 2000) (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Print Magazine (Sept./Oct. 2006) (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Print Magazine (Oct. 2010) (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Sightlines - vol. 12 no. 2 (Winter 1978/79), vol. 12 no. 4 (Summer 1979), 1978; 1979 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Sightlines - vol. 18 no. 3 (Spring 1985), vol. 18 no. 4 / vol. 19 no. 1 (Summer/Fall 1985) (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Sightlines - vol. 19 no. 2 (Winter 1985/86) (2 copies), 1985; 1986 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Sightlines - vol. 19, nos. 3/4 (Spring/Summer 1986), vol. 20 no. 1 (Fall 1986) (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Sightlines - vol. 20 no. 3 (Spring 1987), vol. 20 no. 4 / vol. 21 no. 1 (Summer/Fall 1987) (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Sightlines - vol. 21 no. 2 (Winter 1987/88), vol. 22 no. 2 (Spring 1989), 1987; 1988; 1989 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Take One - The Magazine of the Movies - vol. 6 no. 12 (1978), vol. 7 no. 8 (1979), 1978; 1979 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Trinity News - The Magazine of Trinity Church in the City of New York - vol. 40 no. 3 (1993) (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - The Velvet Light Trap - Review of Cinema no. 24 (Fall 1989) (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Accretions 2012 - Series V: Audio & Video Tape Collection
  - Subseries B: Original Recordings
    - Side A: Dede Allen, AMPAS, NYC, November 7, 2006; Side B: Willis Pyle, NYC, November 9, 2006 (Box 5, Media ID: 040.0265)
      Format: 1/4" audiocassette, Maxell UR 120
    - Leonard Marcus on J.P. Miller, January 15, 2007 (Box 5, Media ID: 040.0266)
    - Charles Solomon on Joe Grant, July 22, 2007 (Box 5, Media ID: 040.0267)
      Format: 1/4" audiocassette, Memorex DBS 90
    - Howard E. Green, LA, July 23, 2007 (Box 5, Media ID: 040.0268)
    - Side A: Carol Grubb, LA, July 23, 2007, part I Side B: Carol Grubb, LA, July 23, 2007, part II (Box 5, Media ID: 040.0269)
    - Carol Grubb, LA, part III, July 23, 2007 (Box 5, Media ID: 040.0270)
    - Jennifer Castrup, LA, July 24, 2007 (Box 5, Media ID: 040.0271)
    - Side A: Andreas Deja, LA, July 25, 2007 Side B: Don Hahn, July 27, 2007 (Box 5, Media ID: 040.0272)
      Format: 1/4" audiocassette, Sony HF 60
    - Side A: Eric Goldberg w. Disney Feature Anim. Studios, July 25, 2007; Side B: Eric Goldberg, Burney Mattinson w. DFA, July 25, 2007 (Box 5, Media ID: 40.0273)
    - Side A: Burney Matinson, July 25, 2007, part II; Mike Gabriel, July 25, 2007, part I; Side B: Mike Gabriel and Burney Mattinson, part II (Box 5, Media ID: 040.0274)
    - John Musker, July 25, 2007 (Box 5, Media ID: 040.0275)
    - Carol Grubb (phone), July 31, 2007 (Box 5, Media ID: 040.0276)
    - Side A: Darla Anderson, Pixar Studio, August 13, 2007; Side B: Darla Anderson continued; Lee Unkrich, Pixar, August 13, 2007 (Box 5, Media ID: 040.0277)
    - Ed Catmull, Pixar, August 13, 2007 (Box 5, Media ID: 040.0278)
    - Side A: Jerome Ranft, Pixar, August 15, 2007; Side B: John Tschudan (childhood friend of Joe and Jerome Ranft), August 15, 2007 (Box 5, Media ID: 40.0279)
    - Side A: Sue Ranft, Corte Madera, CA, August 16, 2007, part I; Side B: Sue Ranft, Corte Madera, CA, August 16, 2007, part II (Box 5, Media ID: 040.0280)
    - Sue Ranft, Corte Madera, CA, part III, August 16, 2007 (Box 5, Media ID: 040.0281)
    - Side A: Brad Bird, Pixar, August 17, 2007; Side B: Andrew Stanton, Pixar, August 17, 2007 (Box 5, Media ID: 040.0282)
    - Side A: Pete Docter, Pixar, August 17, 2007, part I Side B: Pete Docter, Pixar, August 17, 2007, part II (Box 5, Media ID: 040.0283)
    - Bob Peterson, Pixar, August 17, 2007 (Box 5, Media ID: 040.0284)
    - Jonas River, Pixar, August 17, 2007 (Box 5, Media ID: 040.0285)
    - Danielle Workman (phone), August 19, 21, & 22, 2007 (Box 5, Media ID: 040.0286)
    - Brenda Chapman, Pixar, (phone interview), September 12, 2007 (Box 5, Media ID: 040.0287)
    - Tom Wilhite on "Brave Little Toaster" and Joe Ranft, September 14, 2007 (Box 5, Media ID: 040.0288)
    - Jerry and Rebecca Rees (phone), LA, September 21, 2007 (Box 5, Media ID: 040.0289)
      Format: 1/4" audiocassette, Sony HF 90
    - Ruth Ranft (phone - Joe Ranft's mother), October 1, 2007 (Box 5, Media ID: 040.0290)
    - Diane Castrup, NYC, October 4, 2007 (Box 5, Media ID: 040.0291)
    - Side A: Darrell Van Sitters on Joe Ranft, November 27, 2007; Side B: Mike Giaimo (phone), November 28, 2007 (Box 5, Media ID: 040.0292)
    - Side A: Lane Smith (phone), January 2, 2008 Side B: Jorgen Klubien, January 7, 2008 (Box 5, Media ID: 040.0293)
    - John Lasseter (phone), January 15, 2008 (Box 5, Media ID: 040.0294)
    - Susan Goldberg on Joe Grant, February 6, 2008; Carol Grubb (undated); Alice Davis on Joe Grant, LA, February 7, 2008 (Box 5, Media ID: 040.0295)
    - Carol Grubb, February 7, 2008 (Box 5, Media ID: 040.0296)
    - Wendy Wick Reeves (phone) - Nat. Portrait Gal. Smithsonian, March 16, 2008 (Box 5, Media ID: 040.0297)
    - Side A: Tom Schumacher on Joe Grant, NYC, May 27, 2008; Side B: Pam Coats (phone interview), June 3, 2008 (Box 5, Media ID: 040.0298)
      Format: 1/4" audiocassette, Maxell UR 90
    - Dean De Blois (phone), June 4, 2008 (Box 5, Media ID: 040.0299)
    - Andreas Deja, Eric Goldberg, Mark Henn, May 4, 2009 (Box 5, Media ID: 040.0300)
    - Willis Pyle, NYC, July 27, 2010 (Box 5, Media ID: 040.0301)
    - Side A: Michael Sporn, NYC, part I - August 4, 2010; Side B: Michael Sporn, NYC, part II - August 25, 2010 (Box 5, Media ID: 040.0302)
    - Eric Larsen's Brother (undated) (Box 5, Media ID: 040.0303)
      Format: 1/4" audiocassette, Maxell XLII 100
- Accretions 2012 - Series VI: Major Projects
  - Subseries D: Chuck Jones
    - Chuck Jones, 1992; 1997 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Chuck Jones [1 of 2], 1997-2007 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Chuck Jones [2 of 2], 1997-2007 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Chuck Jones - Animation Production Info [1 of 2], 1992-2009 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Chuck Jones - Animation Production Info [2 of 2], 1992-2009 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - The Chuck Jones Center for Creativity, 1988-2003; Bulk 1993, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Chuck Jones - Orig. Transcript - "Memories of Childhood" TCM TV Documentary, 1997; 2008-2009 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Chuck Jones Photos, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Chuck Jones - Turner Classic Movies, 2005-2009 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - MacDowell Medal - Chuck Jones [1 of 2], 1989, 1996-2000; Bulk 1997-1999 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - MacDowell Medal - Chuck Jones [2 of 2], 1989, 1996-2000; Bulk 1997-1999 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Walt Disney Imagineering, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Subseries E: John and Faith Hubley
    - Academy of Motion Picture Arts & Sciences (AMPAS) "Salute to John and Faith Hubley," Los Angeles [1 of 4], 1977, 1996-2012; Bulk 2012 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Academy of Motion Picture Arts & Sciences (AMPAS) "Salute to John and Faith Hubley," Los Angeles [2 of 4], 1977, 1996-2012; Bulk 2012 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Academy of Motion Picture Arts & Sciences (AMPAS) "Salute to John and Faith Hubley," Los Angeles [3 of 4], 1977, 1996-2012; Bulk 2012 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Academy of Motion Picture Arts & Sciences (AMPAS) "Salute to John and Faith Hubley," Los Angeles [4 of 4], 1977, 1996-2012; Bulk 2012 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - AMPAS "Salute to John Hubley" - NYC [1 of 5], 1916-2011; Bulk 2011 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - AMPAS "Salute to John Hubley" - NYC [2 of 5], 1916-2011; Bulk 2011 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - AMPAS "Salute to John Hubley" - NYC [3 of 5], 1916-2011; Bulk 2011 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - AMPAS "Salute to John Hubley" - NYC [4 of 5], 1916-2011; Bulk 2011 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - AMPAS "Salute to John Hubley" - NYC [5 of 5], 1916-2011; Bulk 2011 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Subseries F: "The Moon and the Son"
    - 78th Annual Academy Awards 2005 [1 of 4], 2005-2006 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - 78th Annual Academy Awards 2005 [2 of 4], 2005-2006 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - 78th Annual Academy Awards 2005 [3 of 4], 2005-2006 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - 78th Annual Academy Awards 2005 [4 of 4], 2005-2006 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - John Canemaker Academy Award 2005 "Best Animated Short", 2005-2010 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - John Canemaker Academy Award - Letters of Congratulation, Miscellaneous [1 of 4], 2006-2010; Bulk 2006 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - John Canemaker Academy Award - Letters of Congratulation, Miscellaneous [2 of 4], 2006-2010; Bulk 2006 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - John Canemaker Academy Award - Letters of Congratulation, Miscellaneous [3 of 4], 2006-2010; Bulk 2006 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - John Canemaker Academy Award - Letters of Congratulation, Miscellaneous [4 of 4], 2006-2010; Bulk 2006 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Miscellaneous Information, Congratulation Letters, Emails, Etc., 2001-2009 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - "The Moon and the Son" - A Film by John Canemaker - Production Documents/Correspondence [1 of 3], 1999-2006 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - "The Moon and the Son" - A Film by John Canemaker - Production Documents/Correspondence [2 of 3], 1999-2006 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - "The Moon and the Son" - A Film by John Canemaker - Production Documents/Correspondence [3 of 3], 1999-2006 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Subseries G: "Two Guys Named Joe"
    - Joe Grant Bio/Filmography, Articles/Obits - "Two Guys Named Joe" Book Research, 1941; 1992-2007 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Joe Grant - Caricatures [1 of 3], 1926-1932 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Joe Grant - Caricatures [2 of 3], 1926-1932 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Joe Grant - Caricatures [3 of 3], 1926-1932 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Joe Grant/Dick Huemer "Music Selections by Stokowski and Walt Disney for possible future Fantasia meeting: May 14, 1940" (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Joe Grant. Letters; Story Meeting Drafts; Miscellaneous "Two Guys Named Joe" Book Research, 1934-1941; 1994-1995 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Joe Grant Oral History - Interview by Chas Solomon, March 2000, Academy of Motion Picture Arts and Sciences - "Two Guys Named Joe" (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Joe Grant Personal Interviews - "Two Guys Named Joe", 1985-1990; 1997-2003 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Joe Grant's Family + Early History (Birth Certificate, census records, marriage/death certificate), "Two Guys Named Joe" Research [1 of 2], 1908-1942; 2007-2008 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Joe Grant's Family + Early History (Birth Certificate, census records, marriage/death certificate), "Two Guys Named Joe" Research [2 of 2], 1908-1942; 2007-2008 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Research for "Two Guys Named Joe" Dumbo Original Script, 1940; 2002 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - "Two Guys Named Joe" Book Production Info [1 of 2], 2007-2010 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - "Two Guys Named Joe" Book Production Info [2 of 2], 2007-2010 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - "Two Guys Named Joe" Book Publicity + Promotion, May - October 2010 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - "Two Guys Named Joe" corrected by Walt Disney Archives, version 9/15/08, David Smith and Robt. Tieman, September 15, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - "Two Guys Named Joe" Interviews and Research on Joe Ranft [1 of 2], 1987-2008 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - "Two Guys Named Joe" Interviews and Research on Joe Ranft [2 of 2] (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - "Two Guys Named Joe" Interviews regarding Joe Grant [1 of 2], 1995-2008 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - "Two Guys Named Joe" Interviews regarding Joe Grant [2 of 2], 1995-2008 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - "Two Guys Named Joe" Joe Kennedy's Edit 8/20/08 Excerpts, August 20, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - "Two Guys Named Joe" Joe Ranft and John Canemaker: Personal Correspondence, 1988-2005 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - "Two Guys Named Joe" Picture Selections - Joe Grant and Joe Ranft, undated (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - "Two Guys Named Joe" Research: Dick Huemer, 1942; 1945; 1968; 2006-2008 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - "Two Guys named Joe" Research Portfolio of Art + Correspondence (copies), regarding Joe Grant from his daughter Jennifer Grant Castrup, 1935; 1940-1946; 2005 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - "Two Guys Named Joe" Robt. Cornfeld's Edit 9/8/08 Excerpts, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 20)
- Accretions 2012 - Oversize: Series I - Documentary Material
  - Subseries A: Subjects
    - Irish Animation Research & Article by John Canemaker for Print Magazine Oct. 2010, 1989; 2008-2010 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - NYU Tenure Docket, 1979-1992 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - "Thank You from the KCAI Animation Dept", April 16, 2009 (Map-case 5C)
  - Subseries B: People
    - Canemaker, John - Article for D23 (Disney Magazine) Spring 2012, 2009-2012 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Canemaker, John - in Rio de Janeiro, Brazil Aug. 28 (Mon.) - Sept. 3 (Sun.) 1995. 7th Banco Nacional Int'l Film Festival (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Canemaker, John - Personal Diaries, Notes, Photos [1 of 2], 2006-2012 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Canemaker, John - Personal Diaries, Notes, Photos [2 of 2], 2006-2012 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Accretions 2012 - Oversize: Series VI - Major Projects
  - Subseries D: Chuck Jones
    - Chuck Jones, 1997; 1999 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Chuck Jones, 1997-2007 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Chuck Jones - Animation Production Info, 1992-2009 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Chuck Jones - Orig. Transcript - "Memories of Childhood" TCM TV Documentary [1 of 2], 1997; 2008-2009 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Chuck Jones - Orig. Transcript - "Memories of Childhood" TCM TV Documentary [2 of 2], 1997; 2008-2009 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Chuck Jones - Turner Classic Movies, 2005-2009 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - "Honoring Film Animation Director Chuck Jones", 1997 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Subseries F: "The Moon and the Son"
    - "Congratulations John!" TSOA Students, Faculty, & Staff, Gift to Prof. Canemaker for Winning an Oscar, March 6, 2006 (Map-case 5C)
    - John Canemaker Academy Award 2005 "Best Animated Short", 2005-2010 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - "The Moon and the Son" - A Film by John Canemaker - Production Documents/Correspondenc, 1999-2006 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - "The Moon and the Son" Scene 98, undated (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Subseries G: "Two Guys Named Joe"
    - Joe Grant. Letters; Story Meeting Drafts; Miscellaneous "Two Guys Named Joe" Book Research, 1934-1941; 1994-1995 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Joe Grant's Family + Early History (Birth Certificate, census records, marriage/death certificate), "Two Guys Named Joe" Research, 1908-1942; 2007-2008 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - "Two Guys Named Joe" Book Publicity + Promotion, May - October 2010 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - "Two Guys Named Joe" Book Research, Joe Grant - Caricatures c. 1920/1930's, Joe Ranft - Drawings [1 of 4], undated (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - "Two Guys Named Joe" Book Research, Joe Grant - Caricatures c. 1920/1930's, Joe Ranft - Drawings [2 of 4], undated (Box 8, Folder 23)